Ah but I think it’s..,
wait.
For now,
for,
for now I will tweet.
Long time no see.
Ah but it’s bright.
I think that is better.
I rewatched the live streaming of last time, and the screen was foggy. I was thinking why it is like that, and I think it was my finger that put a fingerprint on the screen. So it was my fingerprint.
Today we can see it well.
Everybody, thank you for sending me your requests for songs. Some that you send to me this morning, I’m not able to cover because I couldn’t practice.
There are some people that send it to me earlier,
and there are some that I can’t sing.
I’m going to sing a few of these, and the songs that I couldn’t cover, I am thinking to do it next week.
These days I want to let my bangs grow. I tried to put my bangs up, but here. Here is long. Here is long but it fits.
Yeah, but, you requested a lot of songs that I already sang in streams before, so I can sing it.
What am I going to sing first. “Yonaderumenou” is high so I'm going to get used to high notes.
It is Menou.
I ate Ryukakusan (mint candy).
But I realised that when I eat Ryukakusan, my natural voice is better, but I can’t sing high notes.
But it is also my vocalization problem.
Wait a little bit.
Hunter Walker san. Thank you for super chat. Thank you. “It’s beautiful” Thank you.
We don’t say “Time” in tag games? Like Time.
Hiroshi san, “Thank you for Yonaderu menou” Thank you for super chat.
Thank you. I’m going to sing Makaroni enpitsu.
It is a little bit low. It is low but I’m going to sing it with one key higher.
It is Makaen’s “Nandemonaiyo”
Good morning. Good morning.
Shelly is Ozaki Yutaka’s Shelly? I just know the chorus.
Time! It is Time!
I’m going to sing “Outsider”
Ok I’m doing it. I am going to sing it with one key higher.
It is “outsider” from Eve san.
“My Rikako’s image is Eve” Maybe from Dramaturgy?
“Is it already spring in Japan?” It was warmer one time, so I thought spring had come but it’s still winter. Like winter and spring. Winter. Spring. Middle. Between. Here.
It is still cold. Cold. Especially today’s wind is cold. Last week’s live stream was a little bit cold, and it was the title of the stream. Yes it is cold. Outside is cold.
I thought that it was warm one time, and I changed my coat to a thin coat, like the one that I put in autumn and spring. Now, I can only go outside with a down jacket because it is so cold.
John Eric san “Hola.” Hola. Thank you for Super chat.
“How much cold is it?” Cold enough to need to wear a down jacket. It is not fun.
“Can you make a spring related song” Tom san. Thank you for Super chat. Thank you.
Make a song related to spring…
Make a song? Hmm…
Relates to spring.
I have to use my imagination. Hmmm…
Doing hanami (cherry blossom viewing)? Hanami.
I never did hanami, but I have an image.
Regarding cherry blossom viewing, I have this image of a caterpillar potentially falling, I wonder about that.
In my recollection, have I ever done hanami. No. no, not in my recollection.
Even I had, I forget things right away.
This is misleading.
How do we say it.
It is not a very old recollection.
Not in my recollection but in my memory. My memory, I want to remember it,
but I forget it.
John Eric san. 「Arigato.」Arigato for the arigato super chat. Thank you.
Are there Caterpillars in spring? I have an image of that.
Long time ago, I tasted the nectar of cherry blossom petals, and I was sipping it without thinking.
It was bad and bitter.
Is there poison in the petals of cherry blossoms?
No?
It was very bitter. I thought that it would be sweet like azalea.
It’s sad. The appearance looks so yummy though, like sakura mochi.
Sakura mochi have a sweet image, so I thought that it(sakura nectar) would be tasty.
Pocket change san. Thank you for super chat. Today’s wind is strong.
Azalea have poison. But I was sipping it a lot.
Maybe in sweet nectar, there is some poison.
So maybe there is no poison in the cherry blossom because it is bitter.
Another one
from request.
It is Aimer.
Ah, yes, last time, I was talking in the live streaming about going to buy some crepe,
but after the stream,
the weather was bad,
and in the end I couldn’t go out. It was raining.
I wanted to eat crepe.
I’m going to sing Calc from Jimmy Thumb.
It was Calc.
Time! Time!
“Hello from Peru” Ok. Hello, thank you. Ok.
I love to use time now.
Maybe I should change how to say it.
Wait a little bit (old samurai japanese).  Wait a little bit. Wait.
I’m going to sing Koiwazurai.
It is Aimer’s Koiwazurai.
What I like from Aimer’s song?
The song that I like the most is probably Kataomoi.
That song is so lovely.
Someone said to me if  there are songs that I can sing of Haniwa (Honey Works), so I’m looking on Ufret for Haniwa.
There is Feat Hoshikawa Sara. Oh, it’s not only seiyuu (voice actor/actress).
Ahh, maybe there aren’t songs that I know. Wait a little.
That song is “Kawaiku Naritai”.
I listened to it a lot when I was in high school.
Clubstar san. Thank you for super chat. Thank you.
“Well done”
AH!! Sorry I spoke too loud.
Recently I realized that my voice is lowest when I speak alone during my live streams. It is what I realized lately.
When I speak with people, we have to interact in real time.
Recently, I’ve noticed that the voice becomes louder and the intonation gets more strong/vigorous, according to the tension of the other party/person.
When I speak alone, … I’m talking to you, but in reality, I speak alone in front of a screen.
So it is like I don’t know. I’m alone. So I cool down.
So, someone requested me “Don’t look back in anger”, so I’m going to sing it.
I am always bad at singing that song.
Shape of you for example feels like a tongue twister for me so I can sing it quite a bit.
It was “Don’t look back in anger”.
This one, when I sing it last time, my C accent was like “swi”, and I received a comment saying that it is better to say “sii”, so I tried.
I think that I improved since last time.
English is difficult.
“Cool” Thank you. Yes, Don’t look back in anger.
I want to sing Shape of you now.
I want to sing it cool.
It is Shape of you.
Hmmm, western music.
I can sing Shape of you, not like the accent
but from a Japanese person’s perspective doesn’t it sound like a tongue twister? I am happy that I became able to comfortably sing Shape of you in an articulate way.
Chiao san, “Ieiri reo Silly Please.’’ Can I sing just the chorus? Thank you for super chat.
I think that I just know the chorus.
There are only 3 lines for the chorus. Sorry. Chorus chorus 3 lines.
Sorry, only that, only chorus. Sorry sorry.
“Listen to Chill beans, it is a cool girls band” Girls band, ok. I’ll take note.
The song was called Paper Hearts,
and there were a lot of people who covered it. From whom do I listen to it?
JUNGKOOK san covered it and other people too so I learned it.
It is difficult and low. Is it really capo 3?
The A melody was difficult. Paper Hearts.
And there is another request, Meru.
It was Meru from n-buna san.
Ok so to finish, I saw the comment “Kinmokusei no yoru” so I’m going to sing it.
I like that song too.
It is very nice.
It feels a little bit nostalgic.
Ok so it is the last song.
It was “Kinmokusei no yoru”.
That sound was from there.
The cloth was drying and maybe it fell. Since the wind is too strong.
So I think that I’m going to finish the stream.
Today there are some songs that I couldn’t sing, and songs that I didn’t practice, so I’m going to try to practice to sing it next week and in 2 weeks.
Nekopon san thank you for superchat.
Let’s meet again!
Today I have to go shopping, but the wind is strong so I don’t want to.
Kanau san “Thank you for the stream” Thank you.
Thank you for coming to my live stream.